fha.com 2019-05-22

# FHA Loan Privacy Policy

## Last Updated: January 1, 2017

1INTRODUCTION

Thank you for visiting FHA.com. This Privacy Policy is an integral part of using our Service, and you must completely agree to them in order to use our Service.

2DEFINITIONS

Throughout this Agreement, we may use certain words or phrases, and it is important that you understand the meaning of them. The list is not all-encompassing and no definition should be considered binding to the point that it renders this Agreement nonsensical:

"FHA.com" refers to our company, known as "First Click Mortgage, Inc."; our Site; our Service; or a combination of all or some of the preceding definitions, depending on the context of the word;

"Service" refers to the services that we provide through our Site, including the information provided through our Site and our Site itself;

"Site" refers to our website, [www.fha.com](https://www.fha.com/);

"User" refers to anyone who visits our Site;

"You" refers to you, the person who is entering into this Agreement with FHA.com.

3INFORMATION COLLECTED

### Identifying Information

We collect certain personal information from you when you sign up to our Service that can be used to identify you, including any information that you submit to us via an online form (which may also be passed to a third party, depending on the purpose of the form). The information we collect from you, to the extent that it is private, is disclosed only in accordance with our Terms of Service and/or this Privacy Policy.

### Non-Identifying Information

Whenever you visit our Site, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your IP address, referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, and Internet Service Provider. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

4USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may use your information to:

  * Enhance or improve User experience, our Site, or our Service.
  * Send e-mails about our Site or respond to inquiries.
  * Perform any other function that we believe in good faith is necessary to protect the security or proper functioning of our Site or Service.

5EDITING / REMOVING INFORMATION

Users may in some cases be able to review and edit the personal information they have provided to us by logging into your account on the Site and editing their account. Although most changes may occur immediately, information may still be stored in a web browser's cache. We take no responsibility for stored information in your cache, or in other devices that may store information, and disclaim all liability of such. In addition, we may, from time to time, retain residual information about you in our backup and/or database.

6COOKIES

We use cookies to track advertisements. For this reason, it is necessary that you enable cookies in your browser, and you hereby acknowledge that we have informed you of our use of cookies and that you consent to our use of cookies in relation to your computer system.

7THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

FHA.com may post links to third party websites on its Site, or direct you to the websites of advertisers or the websites that those advertisers promote. These third party websites are not screened for privacy or security issues by FHA.com, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third party websites.

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to members of the Service or Site. FHA.com bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website. Please review the privacy policy and terms of service for each site you visit through third party links.

8THIRD PARTY INFORMATION ACCESS

Although you are entering into an agreement with FHA.com to disclose your information to us, we do use third party individuals and organizations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts, and others.

Throughout the course of our provision of our Service to you, we may delegate our authority to collect, access, use, and disseminate your information. For example, our web host stores the information that you provide us, and we may hire outside contractors to perform maintenance or assist us in securing our website.

It is therefore necessary that you grant the third parties we may use in the course of our business the same rights that you afford us under this Privacy Policy. For this reason, you hereby agree that for every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.

9RELEASE OF YOUR INFORMATION

At times it may become necessary, for legal purposes, to release your information in response to a request from a government agency or a private litigant. You agree that we may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. We may also proactively report you, and release your information to, third parties where we believe that it is prudent to do so for legal reasons, such as our belief that you have engaged in fraudulent activities. You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants.

10EMAILS AND COMMUNICATIONS

By providing information to the Site that forms the basis of communication with you, such as contact information, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited email from FHA.com since, by providing such information, you agree to receive commercial and non-commercial communication from us or anyone else covered under this Privacy Policy. However, you may unsubscribe from certain communications by notifying FHA.com that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information and we will endeavor to remove you from the database.

11SECURITY MEASURES

We take certain measures to enhance the security of our Site and Service, such as using SSL certificates. However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your information. It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

12YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

FHA.com permits residents of California to use its services. Therefore, it is the intent of FHA.com to comply with the California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575-22579. If you are a California resident you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the Californian privacy statutes. In summary, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. You may contact us with any questions at: 

13INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER

Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, FHA.com transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

14AMENDMENTS

Like our Terms of Service, we may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will place a note on our Site as to when this Privacy Policy was last modified. You must read this page each time you access our Service, and your continued use of our Service constitutes your agreement to any amendments.

Should you have any questions concerning Privacy Policy issues, e-mail us: 

Last Modified: January 1, 2017

PLEASE PRINT AND RETAIN A COPY OF THIS AGREEMENT FOR YOUR RECORDS.

### FHA.com Reviews

FHA.com is a one-stop resource for homebuyers who want to make the best decisions when it comes to their mortgage. With our detailed, mobile-friendly site, individuals can access information about different FHA products, the latest loan limits, and numerous other resources to make their homebuying experience easier. Take a look at some of the reviews from other FHA.com visitors!
